leanbellybreakthrough.com 2019-03-17

# Lean Belly Breakthrough

### Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy covers only our on-line information collection and use practices. Please note that your use of the Site and services is subject to the Lean Belly Breakthrough [terms and conditions.](http://www.leanbellybreakthrough.com/terms.html)

**1\. Information collected from you.** Information about your internet connection (IP address) is automatically collected from you. We may also collect "profile" information, such as information regarding your physical health, health conditions, and nutrition and exercise habits. This information does not identify you personally.

**2\. Information you provide.** In order to use this site and to improve communication with you, we may ask that you provide personally identifiable information. By providing such information, you consent to our collection and use of this information, as described herein. Your Personal Information includes all information you provide during the registration process and subsequently.

**3\. Security of the information you provide.** The information you provide during sign-up is protected by our "SSL" Secure Socket Layer. All other pages are fully encrypted. We strive to protect your information through measures to protect our system, however, security cannot be guaranteed. Therefore, we do not ensure or warrant the security of information you transmit, and you do so at your own risk.

**4\. Cookies.** While viewing our site, we use cookies to differentiate you from others. We also use cookies to find out how you arrived at our website. Cookies do not allow us to gather further personal information about you. We simply use this information to improve our site and services.

**5\. Linked Sites.** We may provide links on our Site to other sites that may be of interest to our members. However, these sites are neither reviewed nor endorsed nor do we guarantee that these sites will abide by this Privacy Policy.

**6\. Our Business Structure.** We are a corporation that licenses the use of our technology to other business entities. We assume no responsibility for the privacy practices or violations of our licensees.

**7\. Changes to Policy.** We may change this Privacy Policy from time-to-time. However, if a change is made, we will post the revised Privacy Policy on this Site.

ClickBank is the retailer of products on this site. CLICKBANK速 is a registered trademark of Click Sales, Inc., a Delaware corporation located at 917 S. Lusk Street, Suite 200, Boise Idaho, 83706, USA and used by permission. ClickBank's role as retailer does not constitute an endorsement, approval or review of these products or any claim, statement or opinion used in promotion of these products.
